vaporauthority.com 2018-02-12

# Privacy Policy

  * Privacy Policy

**Vapor Authority Privacy Policy**

**What Specific Information Does Vapor Authority Collect?**

When you register on the website, make a purchase, enter into one of our contests, reply to an email or a survey, or otherwise partake in any site feature, Vapor Authority collects certain information from you.

When you register with Vapor Authority or place an order, you may be asked for your full name, your current email address, your current mailing address, the best number to reach you on, the credit card number you wish to use, and other applicable information necessary to complete the transaction. However, please rest assured that your sensitive credit card information is securely held within our merchant bank’s encrypted servers. However, you do have the option to checkout as a guest, should you wish to remain anonymous.

In the event that your purchase is placed as a gift to another individual, Vapor Authority may also request information about the person who will be receiving the package. This is solely meant to complete the transaction, and the information will absolutely not be used for any other purpose, such as marketing.

As with the vast majority of websites, Vapor Authority does use cookies in an effort to help improve your shopping experience. Vapor Authority gathers general information related to our visitors in order to help make the company as up-to-date and applicable as possible.

Additionally, government regulations require us to verify your age to ensure that you are old enough to purchase electronic cigarette products in your state. In order to accomplish this, your date of birth must be collected and processed through our third-party age verification systems. This information is solely used for the purpose of verifying your age, and is not used for any other purpose whatsoever. You date of birth is never shared, sold, or otherwise utilized for any reason other than for age verification purposes.

**How Does Vapor Authority Use Your Information?**

When you register on the website, make a purchase, enter into one of our contests, reply to an email or a survey, or otherwise partake in any site feature, Vapor Authority collects certain information from you. This gathered information may potentially be used in the following fashions:

In an effort to offer you a personalized shopping experience, and provide you with products and information that is applicable to you specifically.

In order for us to have the ability to serve you when responding to any of your customer service needs or requests.

In order to efficiently and expeditiously process and complete all of your transactions.

To run and manage current promotions, contests, surveys, or other Vapor Authority website features.

In the event that you have signed up to our newsletter, you will periodically be sent Vapor Authority newsletters to the email address you provided when you signed up. You can always opt-out of the newsletter at any time, should you wish to do so.

**How Does Vapor Authority Protect Your Information?**

Vapor Authority applies an array of security measures in an effort to safeguard your sensitive personal information. All of your personal information is housed within secured and encrypted servers, which is only accessible by a very small group of authorized individuals who have been granted access to said information.

When your order has been placed, the transaction is 100% secure. You can ensure that this is the case when you see the url begin with “https:,” which indicates a secured and encrypted page. All of your sensitive personal information, including your credit card information, is wholly conducted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. This information is additionally encrypted within secured databases, which can only be accessed by a very limited amount of authorized individuals.

**Does Vapor Authority Use Cookies?**

Vapor Authority does use cookies. Cookies are nothing more than tiny files that websites transfer onto the visiting computer’s hard drive, provided your web browser setting allows for the use of cookies. Cookies permit the website’s system to identify your specific browser and gather specific information from it. As an example, Vapor Authority utilizes cookies in order to assist us in remembering the specific items that have been added to your shopping cart. Furthermore, cookies help Vapor Authority to identify your personal preferences based on your activities when you visit the website. This information greatly assists us in offering you a superior shopping experience. More generally, cookies afford us the ability to gather website data related to our traffic and interaction, which provides us with necessary tools that can be used to improve the website as a whole.

Regardless of the particular web browser you use, you will always have the option to either not accept cookies or to be alerted any time a cookie is being placed into your hard drive. This can be done through the settings of your website browser. In the event that you elect to turn your cookies off altogether, you will not be able to enjoy many of the benefits that help make your shopping experience much smoother, easier, and more pleasant.

**Does Vapor Authority Sell or Otherwise Reveal Gather Information to Third Parties?**

Absolutely not. Vapor Authority never sells or otherwise transmits any of your information to any third party whatsoever. The term “third-parties” does not include our website hosting partners, or other companies or individuals that help us in managing the website. The one and only time your information may be handed to a third party is when necessary to do so. This may include handing the information over to law enforcement, or when necessary to protect right, liberties, property, or safety of persons.

**Can I Opt-Out of Newsletters After I Have Signed Up?**

Yes, you absolutely can. You can exclude yourself from receiving newsletters at any time you wish. Each newsletter will have a link at the bottom that will afford you the ability to opt-out of any future newsletter, should you wish to do so. Please keep in mind that Vapor Authority routinely offers newsletter subscribers private deals, sales, and coupon codes that are not made available to the public.

**Does Vapor Authority Link to Third Parties?**

No, Vapor Authority does not work with or link to any third party. The one and only third party link that is placed at the bottom of our website pages is to Shopify, which is our web hosting platform company, as well as links to Vapor Authority’s various social media pages.

  **Does Vapor Authority Ever Make Changes to Its Privacy Policy?**

Yes. Vapor Authority may update or otherwise modify the listed Privacy Policy. Each and every time this is done, the specific policy changes will only affect information gathered after the policy has been changed. Moreover, each time the Vapor Authority Privacy Policy is changed or modified, we will make that evident in this section by detailing the specific date such a change took effect. **The Vapor Authority Privacy Policy was last updated on January 30, 2016.**

**Your Agreement and Consent:**

By visiting and using the Vapor Authority website, you hereby consent to all of the terms listed in this Privacy Policy section.
